

AGA ATMAJA FRONT END ENGINEER

CONTACT



ADDRESS

Cepu Kidul Ir.2 no. 3 Blora



DATE OF BIRTH

31 January 1992



PHONE

+62 812 1355 1169



E-MAIL

agacatur@gmail.com



PROFILE & PORTFOLIO

https://agacat31.github.io/myprofile/

LANGUAGES





SKILLS



PROFILE

Accomplished front-end developer with extensive experience building websites, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, and various web scripting technologies, web standards and project management.

Well experienced in SASS/SCSS, VueJS, Ajax, Jquery, Bootstrap, and Responsive Web. Good in GIT, Webpack, and PHP.

ACHIEVEMENTS

2017 ADEPTFORMS

Adeptforms automates Every Process Paper to Paperless. Build forms in minutes, distribute online, receive immediate respons.

2016 GDI ANALYTICS

GDI Analytics is the merge version of IRIS and POLARIS. So GDI Analytics has same features as IRIS and POLARIS.

2015 IRIS & POLARIS

2014 Iris is an Instagram analytics, Polaris is Facebook and Twitter Analytics. Both has same features such as Keyword mapping, Engagement, Post Impression, and many more.

EDUCATION

2011 - 2014

Informatics Management at Universitas Dian Nuswantoro Semarang, Jawa Tengah.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2016 - NOW • ADEPT VENTURE PTE. LTD.

An IT Singapore based company.
Developing Software Solutions, Improving Company's software capability.

2014 - 2016 PT GDILAB

Worked as Front End Engineer. Developing good UI/UX, implementing Ajax, Web Interaction.

2014 • FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPMENT

Some projects while study in college.